[
    {
        "question": "人才",
        "answer": "nhân tài",
        "explanation": "人才 nhân tài"
    },
    {
        "question": "大王",
        "answer": "đại vương",
        "explanation": "大王 đại vương"
    },
    {
        "question": "人天",
        "answer": "nhân thiên",
        "explanation": "人天 nhân thiên"
    },
    {
        "question": "人小",
        "answer": "nhân tiểu",
        "explanation": "人小 nhân tiểu"
    },
    {
        "question": "夫人",
        "answer": "phu nhân",
        "explanation": "夫人 phu nhân"
    },
    {
        "question": "人主",
        "answer": "nhân chủ",
        "explanation": "人主 nhân chủ"
    },
    {
        "question": "人口",
        "answer": "nhân khẩu",
        "explanation": "人口 nhân khẩu"
    },
    {
        "question": "六人",
        "answer": "lục nhân",
        "explanation": "六人 lục nhân"
    },
    {
        "question": "不二",
        "answer": "bất nhị",
        "explanation": "不二 bất nhị"
    },
    {
        "question": "小人",
        "answer": "tiểu nhân",
        "explanation": "小人 tiểu nhân"
    },
    {
        "question": "不一",
        "answer": "bất nhất",
        "explanation": "不一 bất nhất"
    },
    {
        "question": "一人",
        "answer": "nhất nhân",
        "explanation": "一人 nhất nhân"
    },
    {
        "question": "主人",
        "answer": "chủ nhân",
        "explanation": "主人 chủ nhân"
    },
    {
        "question": "入口",
        "answer": "nhập khẩu",
        "explanation": "入口 nhập khẩu"
    },
    {
        "question": "人中",
        "answer": "nhân trung",
        "explanation": "人中 nhân trung"
    },
    {
        "question": "水火",
        "answer": "thuỷ hoả",
        "explanation": "水火 thuỷ hoả"
    },
    {
        "question": "大夫",
        "answer": "đại phu",
        "explanation": "大夫 đại phu"
    },
    {
        "question": "大才",
        "answer": "đại tài",
        "explanation": "大才 đại tài"
    },
    {
        "question": "三千",
        "answer": "tam thiên",
        "explanation": "三千 tam thiên"
    },
    {
        "question": "天水",
        "answer": "thiên thuỷ",
        "explanation": "天水 thiên thuỷ"
    },
    {
        "question": "不才",
        "answer": "bất tài",
        "explanation": "不才 bất tài"
    },
    {
        "question": "六天",
        "answer": "lục thiên",
        "explanation": "六天 lục thiên"
    },
    {
        "question": "天王",
        "answer": "thiên vương",
        "explanation": "天王 thiên vương"
    },
    {
        "question": "大水",
        "answer": "đại thuỷ",
        "explanation": "大水 đại thuỷ"
    },
    {
        "question": "大川",
        "answer": "đại xuyên",
        "explanation": "大川 đại xuyên"
    },
    {
        "question": "人文",
        "answer": "nhân văn",
        "explanation": "人文 nhân văn"
    },
    {
        "question": "太太",
        "answer": "thái thái",
        "explanation": "太太 thái thái"
    },
    {
        "question": "二十",
        "answer": "nhị thập",
        "explanation": "二十 nhị thập"
    },
    {
        "question": "千人",
        "answer": "thiên nhân",
        "explanation": "千人 thiên nhân"
    },
    {
        "question": "大木",
        "answer": "đại mộc",
        "explanation": "大木 đại mộc"
    }
]